wannameet.com 2016-03-25

# Privacy Policy — WannaMeet

## Information we collect

Information collected automatically: When you use WannaMeet, we automatically collect and store information about your computer or mobile device and your activities. This information includes:  

  * Your mobile device's geographic location while the app is actively running
  * How long you used WannaMeet and which services and features you used
  * The online or offline status of WannaMeet

## Information you choose to provide

In order to register, you will be asked to sign-in using your Facebook (or VK) login. If you do so, you authorize us to access certain Facebook (or VK) account information, including information about your Facebook (or VK) friends who might be common Facebook (or VK) friends with other WannaMeet users. By allowing us to access your Facebook (or VK) account, you understand that we will obtain and share your name and a profile picture, as well as the name and profile picture of your Facebook (or VK) friends who are common Facebook (or VK) friends with other WannaMeet users in your network or geolocation.

Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable screens or pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information.

You may also (but are not required to) provide information about yourself (such as your gender, location, URL, or a biography). Any additional image or information you provide may be publicly displayed. If you wish, we will delete your account information; to do so, please close your account by sending an email to help@getwannameet.com

## Information about others

We may collect and store personal information about other people that is available to us through your Facebook (or VK) login, namely the name and picture of certain of your Facebook (or VK) friends as follows: we will only share this information with other WannaMeet users who are already friends with your Facebook (or VK) friend and who already have access to such information.

## How we use your information

We use your information to provide and improve our services, award loyalty points to you, make special offers, customize services for you, better understand our users, diagnose and fix problems, and sell and display offers and ads that may be relevant to you.

## Information about geolocation

While the WannaMeet application is in use, we keep track of your device’s geographic location so that we can connect you to other WannaMeet users based on your particular geographic location.

## Use of your information by others

We may disclose any information: in response to a legal request, such as a subpoena, court order, or government demand; to investigate or report illegal activity; or to enforce our rights or defend claims. We may also transfer your information to another company in connection with a corporate restructuring, such as a sale or merger.

## Children's privacy

We do not allow persons under 18 to register for any service, and we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from persons under the age of 18.

## Information from users outside Singapore

If you’re outside Singapore, your information will be sent to and stored in Singapore, where our servers are located. By using WannaMeet, you agree to the information collection, use, and sharing practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## List of Features and Review of WannaMeet App

There's no doubt that the evolution of communication technology, embodied primarily by smartphones has changed the way we communicate, and even how we establish relationships. In the old days, if you wanted to meet someone to see if there was a spark, you'd have to set up a first-date, find out about the other person and sometimes endure an evening of dead space between the useless banter. But no longer.

Now there are apps that take all the guesswork out of meeting someone you'd actually want to spend time with, and the latest entrant into this field is WannaMeet The application provides a platform for free dating experience. Let's take a look at what the app offers you and how it stacks up in the already-crowded field of social networking.

### Features

Alright, so what you want to know is how does this app work and what does it offer me that's cool? Price: There is no charge to download the app onto your smartphone or tablet, which is always a plus. Nothing worse than spending money on an app that doesn't add anything to your social life, and actually makes you pay for the privilege of being disappointed.

**Languages:** WannaMeet Works in 30 different languages, so no matter what country you were born in, this dating application can accommodate your language needs. English is the primary language, but WannaMeet Also offers Arabic, French, German, Greek, Hebrew, Simplified Chinese, Traditional Chinese, Japanese and Italian.

**Age Recommendation:** Because WannaMeet! Offers you the chance to post sexy images of yourself, you have to be at least 18 years of age to download the app. This hook up app is meant to attract people who like what they see and read about another person, and thus gives you the freedom to post photos that are suggestive and enticing depending on your own natural inhibitions or lack thereof.

**Device Compatibility:** To use the WannaMeet The app you must have iOS 6.1 version or higher. The application works on iPod Touch, iPads and iPhones with version 5 or higher.

**Profile:** Upload your relevant details to create an attractive profile that others can browse to see if they're interested in contacting you. Your profile includes the option of adding a main image of yourself as well as the different languages you speak, interests such as sports, social activities and anything else that you think others will find interesting about you.

**Location:** WannaMeet! Pings your location and shows you other members within your geographic area who may be of interest to you. The app's GPS works throughout the world, so even if you're traveling out of town, you'll still be able to socially interact with other WannaMeet! Application users.

**Matchmaking:** After you've entered your profile information, including any kind of sexy, pensive or playful photo, the application lets you surf through the profiles and photos of the other WannaMeet users. If you find someone interesting while you're surfing, you click on a rectangular box at the bottom of your phone that says WannaMeet' Then you wait to see if the person you've asked to meet hits you back, at which point, you'll see a message at the top of your phone that says, It's a match!' followed by the name of the person you're interested in and a message that he wants to meet you as well.
